Navil Faisal

Web Developer

Web developer with over 2 years of experience analyzing, designing, developing, and integrating front-end & back-end-based applications. Possesses knowledge of web applications using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Laravel, PHP and React.js. Eager to tackle challenging projects, having led teams and successfully deployed innovative web applications, positively impacting business growth and user engagement.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full Stack PHP & Laravel Developer

August 2023 - Present

Mediatrenz pvt ltd, Noida 63, UP

RANGER RENOVATION

It is an API project. App name is Ranger Renovation. It is built on Laravel+React+Inertia. It has Multi Auth Admin panel, Dependent dropdown, and many more and it was an Individual project build by me.

IBY OUTLET

This is a team project on Laravel+React+Inertia which I am working on since September Laravel+react crud, validation, laravel search,login and sign up from laravel/breeze ,multi auth and pagination using components and many more.

CYBERSURANCE.NET

It is also individually made by me where validation was through ajax,php mailer,and many more.

AUTOMOBILEGLASSCO.NET

This is also individually made by me where validation was through ajax,php mailer,and many more.

Core PHP Developer

Sept 2022 - Dec 2022

TRS IT Solution Palam, Palam, Delhi

- Creating and managing content for websites.
- Designing and developing database-driven web.
- Creating and implementing web services and APIs.
- Developing applications using PHP, HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
- Experience with project management frameworks...

CONTACT

- 344 DDA Janta flat Badarpur New Delhi
- · +91-7985595165
- · navilfaisal00@gmail.com
- · linkedin.com/in/navil-faisal
- · github.com/navilll
- https://portfolio-git-main-navilsprojects.vercel.app/

SKILLS

Technical:

- · LARAVEL+INERTIA+REACT
- HTML
- · CSS
- · JAVASCRIPT
- · REACT.JS
- · PHP
- ANDROID APP DEVELOPMENT USING KOTLIN
- · GIT & GITHUB
- · MYSQL
- · TAILWIND
- BOOTSTRAP
- · POSTMAN

Interest:

- Reading Books
- · Playing Badminton
- · Coding

Language:

- · English
- Hindi

EDUCATION

B. Tech

Guru Tegh Bahadur Institute of, Technology, Computer Science Delhi, 2019 — 2023

10th

Sunbeam School Lahartara Varanasi, 2017

12th

Sunbeam School Lahartara Varanasi, 2019

STRENGTH

- · Effective Problem Solver
- · Collaborative Team Player
- · Attention to Detail